Subtitles by explosiveskull
Mommy?
Matthew!
Sophie! No! Don't look!
Close your eyes!
Hello?
No, no, I'm fine, I'm just...
I'm just running.
Okay... okay, I'm on my way.
The first
diagnosis is a delusional disorder.
If the subject believes it to be
real, whether imagined or not,
the delusion exists
and should be treated as real.
This is the first step
in a successful diagnosis.
You with the crime scene?
Dr. Fuller, psychologist.
- Dr. Fuller?
- Uh-huh.
Helena Wynsfield.
Murdered her husband.
We just need to evaluate
her state of mind.
Should be easy...
even for a rookie.
Matthew Wynsfield, 43.
Why are you showing me this?
Because before you make the call
whether Mrs. Wynsfield
is going to the court
or the nut house,
you need to understand the reality
of what we're dealing with.
What'chu got?
I don't know. Taka...
Takahas?
Mrs. Wynsfield?
Can you hear me?
Where is the daughter?
Upstairs with her grandpa.
She's not talkin' either.
Come in.
Hello. Is Sophie here?
She's under the bed.
Shouldn't you be out
looking for the real killer?
- Excuse me?
- He's a drug addict. His name's Dougie.
I saw Helena and Matthew
with him last week.
Please, sir, I just need
a couple of minutes.
Sophie? Would you like to
come out and chat?
Okay, I'm coming in.
Oh, and who is this
fine-looking gentleman?
Mr. Fluffy Jojo.
Well, hello, it's so lovely
to meet you!
I'd love a picture
for my wall.
How about you draw
Mr. Fluffy for me?
When I was a little girl, I used
to have a hideout just like this.
A place where
no one could find me.
I'd go there
when I wanted to be alone...
when I felt a little sad,
because... my mommy was so sick.
Just like your mommy.
Grandpa said if I talk to you,
you'll take Mommy away.
Well, Grandpa is right
to be worried.
We're all worried.
Did your mommy have to go away?
Yes. She had to go
into the hospital.
- Forever?
- Just until she got better.
Did she get better?
Yes, she got better.
And I want your mommy
to get better, too.
You have to be brave
and tell me anything that
you remember from last night.
If I tell, promise you won't
take Mommy away?
I promise.
I heard scary noises.
I went to see
what was happening, and...
And... what did you see?
Sophie? Who hurt Daddy?
Mara.
Mrs. Wynsfield?
Helena?
I just spoke to Sophie.
Who's Mara?
Matthew was barely sleeping,
he was losing his mind...
and he, he broke down and he, he
said he had a confession, and he...
It's okay, Helena.
Take your time.
He'd said he'd cheated on me,
with a student.
We've got a motive.
Ten years of marriage,
just gone.
I said I wanted a divorce.
He begged me, he begged me to
forgive him but I just, I couldn't!
Not even for Sophie.
And then every time
I looked at her, I just, I...
I felt so guilty.
And now he's dead.
What happened last night,
Helena?
Uh, um...
I... I woke up...
completely paralyzed.
I was pressed down
into the mattress.
There was something evil
in the room.
And then I...
I heard this awful music.
And then I saw it. Her.
As real as you're sitting there.
The sleep demon. Mara.
And there was nothing
I could do.
She climbed up on...
onto his chest and... and...
I know how this sounds!
But I... I swear.
I swear on my daughter's life,
I did not kill my husband!
Oh, she's gone.
Certifiable froot-loop.
Uh, get me your evaluation
by tomorrow morning,
then we can mop this thing up.
Sophie just lost her dad.
I need to be sure
before I commit her mom.
Are you kidding me?
We got two options here:
now, either Mrs. Wynsfield is
insane and a danger to the public,
or she's telling the truth,
and a demon killed her husband.
Now, which one sounds more
plausible to you, Dr. Fuller? Hmm?
Certifiable froot-loop!
I'm sorry, Sophie.
- I love you, Mommy.
- I love you, too.
And what did Grandpa
give you for breakfast? Huh?
Pancakes,
with sugar and chocolate.
- Sugar and chocolate?
- Mmm-hmm.
That is naughty.
That is not good. And you
got your little pizza in?
Mmm-hmm.
Good girl.
Oh, could you give her a little more
time please, she's with her daughter.
No can do. Running late.
I gotta get home.
Mrs. Wynsfield,
I'm sorry, but time is up.
Can you come with me?
Please come with me.
What is this? No!
Get off of me! No!
I'm innocent,
I didn't do anything!
- Mommy!
- I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
- You promised!
- I'm sorry.
You promised!
Mommy!
The commerce department
said new home sales increased 3.1%...
"Takahashi knows more,
one-nine-six-six Grange Avenue."
Hello?
Mr. Takahashi?
Who was he?
Don't know.
Not a registered US citizen.
These injuries match those
of the Wynsfield murder.
Whoa, whoa... Now there are
similarities, granted,
but nothing solid enough
to suggest the same killer.
What about the picture?
This guy died over a week ago.
Now what's to say Helena
didn't kill them both?
What? There's no way
Helena did this!
Twisted a guy's head around?
What about this
Dougie character?
- We need to question him...
- We?
Let me remind you
of our roles here, Dr. Fuller;
you're the psychologist,
I'm the detective.
I do the detective work,
plain and simple.
- But I have to put this right...
- Thank you, Dr. Fuller.
Hello, Helena.
Helena, do you know
a Hideo Takahashi?
Your father told me
about someone called Dougie.
A drug addict?
Look...
when I was
around Sophie's age,
my mom started acting strange.
She thought the TV
was talking to her,
and the government
was spying on her.
She went out and bought
this cheap plastic ornament,
a Chinese beckoning cat.
She really, really believed
it would protect her.
It didn't.
Around six months later she was
diagnosed with schizophrenia.
My dad couldn't cope.
He had her committed.
And, three weeks later,
she hung herself.
All I have left of her
is that stupid cat.
My mom is the reason
I became a psychologist.
I know what
Sophie's going through.
I made a mistake, Helena,
and I want to fix it.
Please help me make it right.
Uh... Matthew always had
a sleep problem.
I wanted to help him,
so I... I...
I found a support group
for sufferers in the city,
run by a Dr. Ellis.
Like a...
an Alcoholics Anonymous
for people who suffer
sleep paralysis.
Is, is that where you met
Takahashi and Dougie?
Meeting other sufferers
really helped Matthew.
He... he came home, he was...
he was feeling much better.
But that night, he...
he woke up paralyzed,
a red mark in his eye.
Then things took a turn
for the worse.
He saw her.
It's okay.
Please, let me go home
and see Sophie, please!
I promise you,
we will find Matthew's killer.
I told you! My husband
was killed by a sleep demon!
Helena...
Helena, listen to yourself...
Look!
She marked me!
She's pure evil,
and she's coming for me!
And if you don't get me
out of here soon,
I will die here, alone.
Please...
There are
three states of being:
awake, asleep,
and somewhere in between.
When coming in and out
of REM sleep,
a hormone is released
into the brain.
This suppresses all body-motor
function, paralyzing the sleeper.
It's actually a handy
little trick of nature;
prevents us from
acting out our dreams.
Some people wake up while in this
state, paralyzed but fully aware.
Some people suffer hallucinations,
waking nightmares.
Almost everyone in their lifetime
will experience sleep paralysis.
And no one
talks about it
because of the stigma of
insanity, but crazy you are not.
So these sessions are here
to provide a forum for people
to speak openly
about their experiences.
So, it's over to you.
Let's hear some of your stories.
I was having a bad nightmare...
the old dream.
I must've been trying
to fight it, 'cause...
When I woke up
I was paralyzed,
and there was something
on my chest. I couldn't move...
...like there was something
in my room... watching me.
- Something evil.
- ...evil.
The Devil. Satan.
I... I couldn't see it...
...but, but it.
It, it was there.
She's here now. She's in
this room watching us.
I see her when I'm awake.
When I'm not paralyzed.
At home... at my church...
Here, now, stalking me.
Saul, who are you talking about?
Haggard old woman,
sent by Satan.
- Mara.
- Dougie please, not again.
Can we let Saul speak?
I swear to God almighty...
she's a demon!
Sent to claim my soul
from Satan!
Saul, whatever you do,
do not sleep!
Dougie, please.
When we come in out of
deep sleep in a sleep paralysis,
sometimes we take
our nightmares with us, okay?
What you saw
was a hallucination.
It's a ghost...
It was no hallucination!
It was the Devil incarnate!
Saul, I'm warning you,
you are in grave danger.
Enough, Dougie, you're scaring him!
It's not real, Saul.
Bullshit!
Dougie.
Saul, Saul...
if you sleep tonight,
you will die.
Dougie!
Please, okay...
Look at this. He's cursed!
Hey! Hey!
Okay, let's all just calm down.
There are no such thing
as curses.
Oh, really? And how the fuck
would you know?
Saul, listen to me,
you see her when you're awake,
and that means
you're in the final stage!
When you get home tonight,
you turn on all the lights.
You get an alarm code,
you get 50 alarm codes!
You get the music,
and you blast it up loud!
You do whatever it is
you need to do to stay awake!
Or you will die tonight!
Oh, God, please don't let...
put their hands on me!
You see this?
This is bullshit!
Mara is real.
She is very, very real,
and she will kill
each and every one of us!
You mark my words,
tonight, Saul dies!
Yo, that is enough!
This is bullshit!
I'm sorry, you okay?
You all right?
You're not listening to me!
Dougie said Saul would die!
Tonight!
That's a real threat, right?
- Mm-mm.
- Maybe Dougie's our killer!
If you get a lead you come to me,
you don't follow it up yourself.
I've just separated
a mother and daughter.
You may not get
how awful that is, but I do.
So, I will put this right.
Enough! Go home now,
while I'm still being nice,
or I will personally see to it that this
is the last homicide case you ever work.
You have
one message. Tuesday, 8:28pm.
Kate, she's getting closer.
I have to see Sophie, please...
to say goodbye...
You put me in here.
Please just, just get me out!
All lines are currently closed.
Patient phone hours
are from 9am to 5pm.
Lord, give us this day
our daily bread,
and forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
Thine is the power
of the grace of the Lord,
forever and ever. Amen.
Jesus, God... purify me!
Purify me, your servant.
This is my journey toward you.
Father who art in Heaven,
deliver me from evil.
Lord forgive me.
Hello?
Dr. Fuller.
What's the matter, you okay?
I'm okay, yeah.
Must've been a bad dream.
I just woke up.
This Dougie character,
did you say he threatened
a man named Saul?
Yes. Why?
'Cause I'm with Saul right now.
Found him living in a dilapidated
shack over on Killhope Island.
Living in the middle of nowhere,
a real hermit.
What did he say?
Not a damn thing.
Figured you could do some,
uh, psychology on him.
Maybe get him to admit
to knowing the victims.
- About before, I... I'm sorry...
- Listen.
What you did
was against procedure.
It was reckless and stupid.
But it did lead to an arrest,
so, let's just consider
the matter closed, all right?
Now...
let's go nail this lowlife.
Time is 15:32, 12th of November.
This is
Lieutenant Mike McCarthy.
Also present is forensic psychologist, Dr.
Kate Fuller.
Suspect is Dougie Trenton.
Mr. Trenton, do you know
a Mr. Takahashi?
No comment.
Matthew Wynsfield?
Saul Conlan?
No comment.
Dougie,
did you kill these people?
No... comment.
Yesterday several witnesses heard
you say that Saul was going to die.
And just like you said, he died.
I didn't kill him. I warned him.
Warned him of what?
This is going nowhere.
Mara.
Tell me about Mara.
You're not the first person
to talk about her.
Help me understand.
I can help you
but you have to talk.
Did you know Mr. Takahashi?
I met him at the group sessions.
He was the first person
to see her.
I mean, I thought...
I thought he was nuts.
But that night,
she came to me, too.
We started looking into it...
Takahashi and me.
You would not believe
the shit that we found.
Mara...
Mara has been killing people
since the dawn of time.
- Did you kill Mr. Takahashi?!
- No... I didn't.
Matthew Wynsfield,
did you know him?
Yeah. And his wife Helena.
But he was marked.
Marked?
Marked, like this!
Oh, I told him,
I warned him, do not sleep!
But he didn't listen.
But once you're marked,
that's it.
It's over.
So this demon,
she marks you first,
and then she kills you?
Yes.
So how come they're all dead,
but you're still alive?
Fuck you.
You know what, I knew this.
I knew you wouldn't believe me.
You want to know what I believe?
I believe you're the only
suspect in three murders!
Suspect all you want, detective.
But you do not have
a single shred of evidence.
- Dougie...
- No comment.
Well, he's right
about one thing,
all we have is hearsay.
He has no alibi,
but no motive either.
Don't look so literally.
Dougie genuinely believes
a demon killed those people.
What if that demon was him?
Another aspect
of his personality.
Still, without any physical
evidence I can't make an arrest.
But we'll keep tabs on him.
He'll slip up sooner or later.
Well, thanks partly to you
we have a viable suspect.
So, I guess Helena Wynsfield can
go home and be with her daughter.
You want to be the one
to give the good news?
So, normally, we would just
bring the patients
to the visiting area,
you know,
they don't really get many
visitors, just to their rooms.
- Yeah, if I had more time
- I would've arranged...
Oh, no, it's not
a problem at all.
Helena?
Helena, you have a visitor...
Someone help! Here!
Someone help!
Helena?
Call 911!
Helena. Go, go! 911! Go!
"Dougie Trenton, old mower
shack, Killhope Island."
- Dougie...
- Go fuck yourself.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait!
I've seen her, too!
What is all this?
Research.
Oh, did you think
it was just you and me, eh?
I don't know
what to think anymore.
Millions of people
have seen it, Kate.
All over the world.
In Japan,
they call it Kanashibari.
In Zanzibar,
they call her Popobawa.
In Canada, they call her
the Night Hag.
But over here, it's Mara.
She's everywhere;
in medieval literature,
art, the Chinese Book of Dreams!
The first recorded evidence
is 400 B.C.
Think about it,
Mara predates Christ!
And look at this, Fuseli...
Fuseli paints her in 1781. 1781!
There must be some other
explanation for all of this.
Yeah? Like what?
I don't know.
- Hallucinations...
- Hallucinations?
Yes.
Hallucinations.
Okay... see these?
These are just some
of the recent sightings!
And what about...
Takahashi,
what about Helena,
what about Saul,
Matthew, me, you?
If these are hallucinations, Kate,
then how come we all see her?
Mara is real,
and she's killed before.
Look at this, eh...
right here, 1977.
One hundred Hmong refugees
die in their sleep
after experiencing an evil
presence crushing their chest!
And then again, 1983 Thailand, 230
people are found dead in their sleep!
Now, no doctor or psycho-fucking-therapist
can explain these deaths!
And now she's here,
and she's killing again!
So millions see her
but she only kills a few? Why?
I don't know,
I haven't worked this out yet,
but there is
some kind of pattern.
She kills in clusters, always,
after a tragedy or an event.
It's like Mara
is in the spirit world
and the tragedy somehow
brings her into our world.
But there hasn't been
any big tragedy here recently.
Well, then maybe
we've missed it.
How do you miss a tragedy?
I'm sorry, Dougie,
but this is crazy!
Please, you have got
to start believing me!
Listen, you're at stage two!
Stage two, what?
It comes in stages,
I've worked this out.
Look, stage one:
you're paralyzed,
and you see her.
Now, millions of people experience this,
but for some, nothing else happens.
For the unlucky ones like us,
it goes to stage two.
She marks you, red in the eye.
This is where you are, Kate!
Then it moves to stage three,
the physical contact.
She climbs up on your chest, she
places her hands around your throat.
And then it's stage four.
Soon, you'll see her
when you're awake,
she'll be in your waking world.
And the next time you sleep...
you're dead.
Well, if this is true,
how come you're still alive?
I only sleep
for 20 minutes at a time.
I've figured out
that Mara only comes
if you're in a deep sleep.
I set all of the alarms, music,
anything I can,
for 20-minute intervals.
I never sleep
for more than 20 minutes.
And that way she can't
get into my waking world.
Dougie, how long has it been
since you had a proper sleep?
I don't know...
A few weeks, a month...
I can't remember.
Do you realize what effect
that will have on your mind?
Dougie, you're severely
sleep deprived!
All this talk
about sleep demons, and...
Kate... you have to
listen to me, Kate!
Now, you can believe all this
science and this forensic bullshit,
but I am telling you right now,
you are marked!
Our only hope is to figure out what
links us all, or we're all dead!
Kate! Kate! Listen to me!
I'm warning you, do not sleep!
Find the link, Kate,
so we can stop her!
Dr. Ellis?
I need to show you something.
It's like an invisible force
is lifting her up
and slamming her back down,
right?
But nothing supernatural.
Convulsions, a seizure.
What about the mark?
Helena had it and now I do, too.
Mark?
- Just a burst blood vessel.
- No, people have died.
- Can you explain that?
- Not without looking into their individual circumstances, no.
What about the Hmong refugees?
Over a hundred died
in their sleep.
- SUNDS.
- What?
Sudden unexpected
nocturnal death syndrome.
It has nothing to do
with sleep paralysis.
Come here,
I want to show you something.
Most sleep labs are clinical,
like hospitals.
But for more accurate results the
patient should feel more at home.
It's tinted, two-way.
The control room's
on the other side.
Thanks, Carly.
So this is where
we monitor the sleepers.
This is all great, but what does
it have to do with Helena's death?
I was just a kid the first time
I got sleep paralysis.
I swear to God,
Freddy Krueger was in my room.
- For me, it was aliens.
- Ah, the generation gap.
Ever since Roswell,
the whole UFO phenomenon,
alien abductions
have increased tenfold.
You mean since the X-Files.
Uh... sorry,
what are you saying?
It's no coincidence that people
share similar hallucinations.
What we see in sleep paralysis is directly
influenced by the culture around us.
Things that scare us.
For me, it was Freddy Krueger.
In the old days, it was witches.
Fast forward to Mulder and Scully
over here and boom, aliens.
Yeah, but Mara
isn't part of our culture.
Why did I see her?
Simple. Helena told you
her sleep demon story.
It scared you,
stayed with you,
and then you suffer
sleep paralysis, and,
as if by magic,
you see the same thing.
I'm telling you, as a scientific
fact, Mara is not real.
And sleep paralysis cannot kill.
You have nothing to fear.
Thank you, doctor.
Mommy?
You left me alone to die!
Hello?
Mr. Wynsfield?
It's Dr. Fuller.
I just want to check on Sophie.
How is she doing?
Terrible. She's not
sleeping right, she's having bad dreams.
It all happened
after you spoke with her.
She's got it in her head that it was
her fault her mother got locked up.
I'm so sorry.
It's the funeral tomorrow,
please, just leave us alone.
We are here today to join...
You have one
new voice message.
Kate, it's Dougie. I fell
asleep, Kate. I'm on stage four!
She's here,
I can't sleep, or I am dead!
You've got to help me, please!
I'm gonna do something.
Bye, Kate, help me!
Mustn't sleep...
stay awake...
Stay awake...
Stay awake... mustn't sleep.
Mustn't sleep.
Mustn't sleep. Stay awake...
Dougie? Dougie!
Dougie!
Oh, God.
- Oh, God... God...
- Kate...
What have you done?
- What have you done?
- She's coming, please...
She's coming, please...
- This is stage four.
- No...
This is stage four!
- She's here, Kate!
- No!
- There's no one here,
there's no one here,
it's just me!
I will, I will, I promise.
You have to trust me, okay?
Hold on, just hold on...
- Kate?
- Dr. Ellis!
- You okay?
- I need help. Dougie's hurt himself.
He's on stage four!
And I've seen it!
Kate, calm down,
just bring him into the clinic!
I can't understand
what's happening...
I can help him here,
trust me, I can help him.
Kate, you're exhausted.
Dougie, too.
All you need is a good night's sleep
and your problems will be over.
I hope you're right.
It'll help calm you.
Any sign
of anything unusual
and we'll wake you up
immediately. I promise.
It's all a waste of time, Kate.
She's got me beat.
You're in safe hands now.
Everything is going to be fine.
I'm right by your side
and I'm not leaving.
I know why she comes now.
I've worked it out.
It's the fucking war.
We were at a checkpoint.
Everything was on edge.
We hadn't slept for days.
Dougie, you don't have to...
Then out of the dust,
a vehicle came toward us. A car.
I signaled for it to stop,
but...
it just kept on coming.
We'd already lost two men,
I didn't want to lose
anybody else.
I opened fire.
Then the car... slowed down...
it stopped.
And that's when I heard...
the crying, and the wailing...
it was the most haunting sound
I've ever heard.
Dougie...
A young woman. A girl.
A mother...
she took a bullet to the chest.
She was bleeding to death.
She was
holding her dead baby.
She looked straight at me...
Oh, God, forget it, Kate.
What the fuck did I do?
The fuck did I do, Kate?
Hush, Dougie...
Sleep, sleep, Dougie.
Everything is going to be okay.
I'm right here.
Sleep now...
Let's get this show on the road.
Subject asleep, 23:45.
Okay, Mara,
let's see what you got.
So much for sleep demons.
Oh, shit!
Carly!
Dougie!
Christ!
Dougie! Dougie!
Wake up! Kate, wake up!
Kate, wake up!
I was watching...
No! No, it can't be!
Oh, my God! Oh my God!
We had him wired,
monitored, I...
I don't know what this is.
It's okay, doctor,
take your time.
I'm a scientist,
I deal with the facts and logic,
not, not this, this...
McCarthy.
Oh, no.
What happened?
Last night
she had some sort of fit,
she stopped breathing.
Now she's seeing things.
Hey... hey...
She's behind you.
Listen, she's in the final stage.
Do not let her sleep.
Please,
if she sleeps, she will die!
Get out!
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
I'll be back, Sophie. I promise.
Just stay awake.
Just keep her awake.
Shit...
Shit... shit...
You are marked!
My husband was killed
by a sleep demon!
You'll see her
even when you are awake...
The next time you sleep,
you're dead.
Taka, Matthew, Saul.
Helena.
Dougie.
Sophie.
Matthew, Helena, Dougie...
What's the link?
Find the link, Kate,
so we can stop her!
I'm warning you, do not sleep!
Sophie...
Takahashi, Matthew...
"Lead the way..."
Oh, Dougie...
The war.
Saul's accident.
Helena? Helena...
He begged for
me to stay, but I just,
I couldn't,
not even for Sophie.
I felt so guilty.
And now he's dead.
You blame yourself
for Matthew's death.
And I blame myself for yours.
Saul killed his mom.
Matthew had an affair.
Dougie killed in Iraq.
In every other outbreak,
there was a big tragedy.
Why not here?
Takahashi.
What did you do?
- Hello?
- Takahashi.
Who is he, what did he do?
Kate, what...
where the hell are you?
Listen to me!
Listen to me,
Takahashi did something!
Something so big, so awful,
that he caused all this.
- What did he do?
- Kate, what... what in the hell...
- Tell me!
- All right, all right, all right.
Back in Japan, he was a chef
in a primary school.
He cut a deal
on some cheap food,
uh, raw fish that
was contaminated, 38 kids died.
He'd been on the run ever since.
That's it, that's the tragedy
- that brought her.
- Brought who?
Mara! Takahashi went on the run,
ended up here.
But he felt so bad for what he had
done that his guilt brought Mara out!
She killed him then spread,
drawn to people's guilt.
The sleep clinic group,
friends and family... that's it!
- That's how she works!
- Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait...
You sound like Dougie, what... what
the hell are you talking about?
Listen to me!
Dougie killed innocents in Iraq,
Saul killed his mom,
Matthew had an affair,
Helena blamed herself
for the divorce,
I had an innocent woman
committed and orphaned Sophie.
- It's guilt!
- What about Sophie?
What does an eight-year-old kid
have to feel guilty about?
- She talked to me.
- What?
Her grandfather told her that if she
talked to me I would lock her mommy away.
Sophie blames herself!
I have to put her right!
Wait, Kate!
Sophie's in the final stage!
Mara is coming for her next!
I have to tell her that none of
this is her fault. I'm to blame!
Wait, wait, Kate, wait!
Dr. Fuller?
Shit!
Helena?
This is the City Cross
Ferry Line, next stop Stanley Park.
...Memorial Hospital.
Yes! I wanted to go!
It was a whole thing.
You bad boy!
Sophie... it's Kate, honey.
There's something
I need to tell you.
Sophie! Sophie, can you hear me?
Sophie, you've done nothing wrong,
it was my fault, not yours.
Soph... wake up!
No! No! No!
Don't you touch her! No!
No, don't you touch her!
I'm the guilty one, not her!
I'm begging, take me, take me, take me...
No! No! Wake up, Sophie!
Wake up!
Wake up...
- Sophie! Sophie...
- I don't blame you.
It's okay. You're innocent, too.
It's okay. It's over.
You can sleep.
Mr. Fluffy looks tired.
Sweet dreams.
Kate? Kate?
Kate?
You okay?
Yeah. How is she?
Doctor says she'll be fine.
I guess it was all in her mind.
Demons only exist up here.
Come on,
you've had a rough night,
let me give you a ride home.
Yeah, thank you.
Just one second.
Morning, Sophie.
I hear you're feeling
much better today.
And so is Mr...
Huh.
Where are the stitches?
I forgive you,
but Mom can't.
Sophie...
I will never forgive you!
You left me alone to die!
Subtitles by explosiveskull